Pizza delivery.
Wow. So, this is a real TV station, huh?
Well, it's a Fox affiliate.
What are you showing right now?
Single Female Lawyer.
It's the season finale. You want to watch?
Ah, I don't know. That's a chick show.
I prefer programs of the genre
world's blankiest blank.
She is wearing
the world's shortiest skirt.
I'm in.
Counselor, I remind you
that it's unethical
to sleep with your client.
If you really care about the outcome
of the case,
you should sleep with me.
Your Honor, it's bad enough
to proposition
a single female lawyer in court,
but this is a unisex bathroom.
Overruled, counselor.
Could you repeat that last part?
Oh, my God! You knocked Fox off the air!
Pfft! Like anyone on Earth cares.
Could you repeat that last part?
This is an outrage!
I demand to know what happened
to the plucky lawyer
and her compellingly short garment.
Due to technical difficulties,
we now bring you
eight animated shows in a row.
What in the name of Bob Marley's ghost?
- Get to work, you lazy boltbag.
- Ow!
Ow!
Hey, quit it, Hermes. It's Labor Day.
Labor Day? That phony-baloney holiday
crammed down our throats
by fat-cat union gangsters?
- That's the one.
- Hot damn. A day off.
Who's up for one last summer beach trip?
- Oh, yeah.
- Ready, Freddy.
Eh, I think I'll just stay here.
Fry, you're wasting your life
sitting in front of that TV.
You need to get out
and see the real world.
But this is HDTV.
It's got better resolution
than the real world.
Everyone's too polite
to say anything,
but you're covered with bedsores.
- Not covered.
- Just get in the car.
Ah! Here we are.
Wait. Mount Rushmore
and the Leaning Tower of Pisa?
- I didn't know they were both in New York.
- They are now.
In the 2600s, New Yorkers elected
a super-villain governor,
and he stole most
of the world's monuments.
Truly a great man. Look at him up there.
Aha!
Found you.
Okay, now you go hide.
Nice knowing you.
Ah!
Come on, Zoidberg.
I passed it right to you.
Ugh! I've had it with this game.
I'm going for a scuttle.
Okay, everyone, come and get it!
Ah! Just like my dad used to make,
until McDonald's fired him.
Bite my red-hot glowing ass.
Wait a minute.
Red-hot glowing ass?
I'll be right back.
Ow! Ow! Ow! Ow! Ow! Ow! Ow! Ow! Ow! Ow!
Oh!
Yeah.
Mmm!
No. Nibbler.
Psst!
Professor, I need another bikini.
Wha...
Oh! Okay. I think there's one can left.
Oh, my.
There. How do I look?
Like a cheap French harlot.
French?
Say, dollface, how'd you like
to make time with a real man?
No. I'm not attracted to bullies,
no matter how big and handsome they are.
It's okay, Leela, go ahead.
I got a lot of work to do here.
Sir, you don't understand.
I'm a professional beach bully.
I pretend to steal your girl,
you punch me, I go down,
she swoons, you slip me 50 bucks.
50 bucks?
Not even if she was my girlfriend.
You take her.
Fry.
Although I suppose we could go
for a walk on the beach.
Uh... No, thanks, ma'am. I'm actually gay.
Uh-oh. Help. Help!
Bender, you got to spring me.
I'll never survive in here.
I'm too pretty.
All right, all right. I'll bust you out.
Cheese it!
Voilà.
The greatest sand castle ever built.
The kind of castle
King Arthur would have lived in
- if he were a fiddler crab.
- It's very nice.
We should get a picture
before the tide comes in.
Oh, yeah. Anyone have a camera?
Right here, buddy.
Wait. I want to be in the picture, too.
Pretend you're happy.
Oh, my God!
What in Babylon?
No!
Faster!
We're all gonna die, aren't we?
Oh, I should think so.
Although, last time aliens invaded
all they did was force
the most intelligent of us
to pair off and mate continuously.
Oh, yes.
Once again, today's winning
lotto number was four.
In other news, alien saucers continue
to rain destruction upon Earth.
We now go live to an emergency address
by Earth president McNeal.
Ladies and gentlemen,our course is clear.
The time has come to knuckle under.
To get down on all fours
and really lick boot.
Give our alien masters
whatever they want and...
People of Earth,
I am Lrrr, of the planetOmicron Persei 8.
Is this thing on?
Now, then.
We want the one you call McNeal.
Give us McNeal,
or we will lay waste to your cities
with our anti-monument laser.
We demand McNeal!
Uh... As I was saying...
mankind would sooner perish
than kowtow to outrageous
alien demandsfor this McNeal...
Whoever he is. Am I right?
And now, the man who will lead us
in our proud struggle for freedom,
fresh from his bloody triumph
over the pacifists of the Gandhi Nebula,
25-star general Zapp Brannigan.
Hey, look, Leela.
It's that idiotic windbag you slept with.
The Earth is under attack.
Can't we just forget about that?
Evidently not.
Call me cocky, but if there's an alien
out there I can't kill,
I haven't met him and killed him yet.
But I can't go it alone.
That's why I'm ordering
every available ship to report for duty.
Anyone without a ship
should secure a weapon
and fire wildly into the air.
Well, you heard the windbag.
We've been drafted.
Everyone into the ship.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa! Hold on!
I refuse to fight.
I'm a conscientious objector.
- A what?
- You know, a coward.
Since this is an emergency,
all robots will now
have their patriotism circuits activated.
It is every robot's duty to give his life
for the good of humanity.
Oh, crap.
You're all from different cultures here.
Some of you are white.
Some of you are black.
You're brown. And you're silver.
But I don't care if your skin's
red or tan or Chinese.
You're all going to have
to learn to die together.
- Am I right, soldier?
- Well, actually, I...
Sir! Yes, sir! Sir!
Remember, our mission is simple.
Destroy all aliens.
Um... Eh... Not me, sir.
Oh, yes. Right. Nobody destroy Kif.
Unless you have to.
Oh, ho, ho.
The luscious Captain Leela.
This is turning into
one very sexy struggle
for the future of the human race.
Thanks, but I'm not technically human.
Right, right.
Nobody destroy Leela, either.
The key to victory is discipline,
and that means a well-made bed.
You will practice until
you can make your bed in your sleep.
You mean, while I'm sleeping in it?
You won't have time for sleeping, soldier,
not with all the bed-making
you'll be doing.
The alien mother ship is in orbit here.
If we can hit that bullseye,
the rest of the dominoes
will fall like a house of cards.
Checkmate.
Now, like all great plans,
my strategy is so simple,
an idiot could have devised it.
On my command, all ships will line up
and file directly
into the alien death cannons,
clogging them with wreckage.
Wouldn't it make more sense
to send the robots in first and...
Sir! I volunteer for a suicide mission!
Ah! Cut it out!
You're a brave robot, son,
but when I'm in command,
every mission's a suicide mission.
Which reminds me...
Leela, perhaps before we head into battle
you'd like to make love to me
in case one of us doesn't come back.
Maybe we should wait till afterwards
in case neither of us comes back.
Here's hoping.
Muah!
I'm gonna be a sci-fi hero
just like Uhura
or Captain Janeway or Xena.
Fry, this isn't TV, it's real life.
Can't you tell the difference?
Sure. I just like TV better.
Bender, damage report.
The auxiliary power's out.
And they spilled my cocktail.
All right, scumwads,
this one's for Bender's cocktail.
We did it! We won!
Yeah, but it'll never
bring back my martini.
Well, who wants a martini?
Good work, everyone.
The mother ship is destroyed.
What the hell is that thing?
It appears to be the mother ship.
Then what did we just blow up?
The Hubble Telescope.
Stop exploding, you cowards!
This is hopeless.
If we're gonna get blown to bits,
we may as well do it
in the comfort of our own home.
You'll be the captain,
you'll be thedelivery boy,
and you'll be the alcoholic,
foul-mouthed...
Oh, God, you're alive!
I mean, thank God, you're alive.
Sorry. Check back in three days.
A week at the most.
We want McNeal! Stop stalling!
And now a rebuttal from President McNeal.
The people of Earth remain united
in my refusal to hand over myself.
Total annihilation is a small
price to pay compared with...
Here he is! Come and get him!
You are not McNeal.
Huh?
You are not the one we want.
Oh! Thank you. Thank you,
glorious masters. I...
Give us McNeal!
That was McNeal.
No, McNeal, the single female lawyer.
She wears miniskirts and is promiscuous.
Really.
Miniskirts?
That sounds familiar.
Surely you know McNeal.
She is an unmarried human female
struggling to succeed
in a human male's world.
Maybe that's just her excuse
for being incompetent.
Silence! We will accept no more decoys.
This is the McNeal.
Wait. I know her.
You do not, you big, fat liar.
You don't know anyone.
All you do is watch TV.
That's where I know her from.
She's Jenny McNeal.
She was a character on a TV show
back in the 20th century.
Single Female Lawyer.
Well, if they're hoping to see a TV show
that hasn't existed for 1,000 years...
They are royally boned.
We will raiseyour planet's temperature
by 1 million degreesa day for five days
unless we see McNeal
at 9:00 p.m. tomorrow, 8:00 central.
Oh! I'm beginning to think
there'll be no forced mating at all.
They're going to destroy the entire Earth
if they don't see
some stupid TV show
about some bimbo lawyer?
It's crazy. How could they even know
about a show from 1,000 years ago?
Well, Omicron Persei 8
is about 1,000 light-years away,
so the electromagnetic waves
would just recently have gotten there.
- You see...
- Magic. Got it.
Check this out.
Back in 1999, the season finale
of Single Female Lawyer
was interrupted by technical problems.
Apparently some zidiot spilled
coke on a transmitter.
Beer. I would think.
They must just want to see that episode.
Let's find a tape and give it to them.
There aren't any copies left.
No, there wouldn't be.
Most videotapes from that era
were damaged in 2443
during the second coming of Jesus.
You know, I saw the first
30 seconds of that episode.
If I could make up an ending,
maybe we could act it out ourselves.
I could make the costumes.
I have an old five megawatt
broadcasting tower in the attic.
And I... I could be an acting coach.
Let's put on a show!
Okay, Leela, you'll be
starring as Jenny, who...
Uh-uh. Forget it.
A, I'm camera shy,
and B, I get tongue-tied
in front of an audience
armed with death rays.
Plus, you don't really have
the thighs for a miniskirt.
Give me the script.
Places, everyone.
Okay.
All set.
Lights.
Camera one.
Camera two.
Camera three.
Prepare the watercooler
that we may gather around it
later and discuss things.
Single Female Lawyer
Fighting for her client
Wearing sexy miniskirts
And bein' self-reliant
Hey, I'm pretty good.
Jenny McNeal,
you are charged with jury tampering
in last week's case
on account of your hot,
naked affair with the foreman.
How do you plead?
Your Honor, I move for a mistrial
on the grounds that
I'm also having a hot, naked affair
with the foreman of this jury.
I'll see you during the recess.
If McNeal wishes to be taken seriously,
why does she not simply
tear the judge's head off?
It is true what they say,
"Women are from Omicron Persei 7,
"men are from Omicron Persei 9."
Your witness, Prosecutor Ramirez.
Gracias.
Single female lawyer,
where were you on the night of August 23?
Sleeping with you.
Aha!
Uh, get...
Getting back to the matter...
Uh, if it please the court...
Fry, there's nothing else here.
You only wrote two pages of dialogue.
Well, it took an hour to write,
I thought it would take an hour to read.
What are we supposed to do now?
I don't know. I don't know.
Just say anything
as long as it's compelling
and mesmerizing.
A tour de force.
Uh...
What say you, single female lawyer?
I say... I'm giving up the law,
and I'm giving up being single.
Your Honor, will you marry me?
Oh, no. Go to commercial.
We'll be back after this word
from crazy Bender's discount stereo.
Married? Jenny can't get married.
Why not? It's clever, it's unexpected.
But that's not why people watch TV.
Clever things make people feel stupid,
and unexpected things
make them feel scared.
Attention, McNeal,
your unexpected marriage plan scares us.
You stole our hearts
as a single female lawyer,
and so shall you remain... Or else.
You see? TV audiences
don't want anything original.
They want to see the same thing
they've seen 1,000 times before.
What you talkin' 'bout, Fry?
Trust me on this. While other people
were out living their lives,
I wasted mine watching TV,
because deep down
I knew it might one day
help me save the world.
Plus, I would've lost my workmen's comp
if I had gone outside.
Now just read these cue cards.
And action.
"Miss McNeal, I'm afraid I must decline
"your offer of marriage,
"for you see, I'm dying.
"Cough, then fall over dead."
"My God, he's dead."
"I will now make my closing statement.
"With my fiancé deceased,
"I hereby return
to my single female lawyer career,
"no matter what any man says."
"We find the defendant
vulnerable yet spunky."
And cut.
Single female lawyer
Havin' lots of sex
Attention, McNeal.
We are reasonably satisfied
with the events we have seen.
Overall, I would rate it a C plus.
Okay, not great.
As a result, we will not
destroy your planet,
but neither will we provide you
with our recipe for immortality.
Way to overact, Zoidberg.
And now we must return
to our planet to catch the end
of a 1,000-year-old Leno monologue.
- You did it, Fry.
- Yep.
It was just a matter
of knowing the secret of all TV shows.
At the end of the episode,
everything's always right back to normal.